Not so bad. Alright, we can circle back,
get this packed. Oh,
boy. Bet you wish you were back in the
office, huh? So,
we've got a few potential topics for
workplace research. One, do the drones
work harder if they're given gourmet
cuisine that they're later told is lab
grown human flesh? But why? Why lab grown?
That part's a lie. Option two. Was that
a groan of excitement? No, it's a groan of
regular grown. N why? With Lanag gone and
us in charge, we can do whatever we want.
But what's the point? I guess I'd say that
these projects let me see myself as more
than a cog in a soulless machine and stir
the cold ashes of my soul, if only for a
moment. Duh. You don't have to explain
self care to me. But then just Lana comes
back, undoes everything, and never leaves
us in charge again. So we have nothing to
look forward to, huh? There a reason you
have this newfound y sense of perspective?
Well, I'm off like 60% of my meds ever
since this stupid horse doctor had to
leave town. I told him the horse cops were
a bad sign. Did he listen? Yeah, I think
those were just cops riding regular
horses. Hey, guys. I just want you to all
work normally and have a normal day,
because apparently that's all we're here
for. Ugh. Leave me. I must brood.
I think you just discovered your secret
weapon. I don't like it. They've got to be
up to something. But what? I say we strike
now, before they get their plans in order,
so we can mess with them and not get
blamed. Perfect. And do we need to add the
human flesh thing to this? Or. God, just
freeze it. What is the point of going
back in if we don't have the detonator?
You should really bring backups for these
kind of important things. I shouldn't even
have to be here. It isn't like we asked
you to come. So I should have just left
this in the hands of a helicopter pilot
who can't fly, a beer drinking co pilot,
and the guy who can't keep track of the
one thing we need to accomplish the
mission. And that.